Subscribe to Stock Market Planner Channel
which select carbon uploading video cola
shat-shaate apna din notification
[Music] If we
say approx but in 3:30 day tomorrow the weather has
negative return
mines 5.6% negative return then approx
6% would have to say
-
3.36% so approx 3:30 day tomorrow the
negative return generated machine performance of these modern
17.98% so approx
18% weather but negative
Amravati left first January
take first January performance
-3.95% then approx 4% would have to say current 4% *
negative return generated fast January
performance
-49.87% negative then approx
50% would have to say * negative feed and
genetic Manipal ji
welcome
stock market company
[Music]
So 100% man investment
then by generating 60% return they are making 5, so it is
right but then five promises of the butter
performance co-ordinates would have to say
maximum
performance then Panchgachhi of Natural Paper Company is maximum  Let's go
to the chapter, maximum
positive
47.21% positive Pritam generate Karzan
approx say 47%
which is the time by maximum, so we have shown the company 2018
because at a little past
five thirty,
47% maximum
so maximum Chatpatent and five promises
[Music]
- 1.3%
negative
1.41% positive
Hack machine
rate
down -
40.40
-23.4% negative
1st January 1st January
Paper wealth create - Stock market
is stock market
so Kon decoration company
2005.25% positive
[Music]
57% I mean 60% means if we
calculate exactly
then return generator
network
sorry this is in short pattern
nature
and I am looking at profit booking and corrections a
lot, so our
collection company
is of one company, but we
keep our own ruler, but our
small cap table company is our bangle
next company next company
Healthcare Limited one company
so one company which  If it is a chapter small cap company then
give your market capitalization and also the small cap company of the company then a company mines 8.23% negative performance - 20.23% negative
-8.85% negative region then approx say
9% but negative hit and generated
first January
-
39.77% negative
in the long term of the company share holder wealth
create
n 5%
take maximum performance
23.76% positive 2019
which
were consider code on positive engineer sweat tarkadunki tarkadu
data history available note
decent vacancy
directly this jamkudi bike
night keep then after date only your decide
company but small company specialty risk
factor glass ko mat
ke company
Balaji but mota-motti data policy